Guide to the Carl Djerassi Papers SC0348
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Lab Notebooks, Series 2
  - Ann-Marie Weidler, Jan. 1961- (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Jan William Simek (from p. 121 on), Nov. 1973-Dec. 1974 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Gerald W. Krakower, Wayne State University, May 1958-July 1958 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Powers (?), July 1958-May 1959 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Vorgrueggen, Sept. 1959-Mar. 1961 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Djerassi Research Group, McCrindle/Burrows (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - B. D. Thomas (? Wayne State University) (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - J. J. Harrison (from p. 90 on), Chem. Dept., Stanford (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Rafat Mirza, Dept. of Chemistry, Wayne University, "Investigations related to Casimiroedine," June 1954-Oct. 1954 (Box 9, Folder 59A)
  - Kjell Undheim (from p. 80 on), Dept. of Chem., Stanford, Sept. 1959 (Box 9, Folder 59A)
  - K.J.L. Thiebery, Nov. 1956- (Box 9, Folder 59B)
  - [unidentified, from p. 147 on], Sept. 1957- (Box 9, Folder 59B)
  - Lynn Wolf, Wayne State University, Jan. 1959- (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Lyn Taylor (from p. 110 on), Stanford, Feb. 1973-May 1975 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Tatsuhiko Nakano, Dept. of Chemistry, Wayne State University, Sept. 1956-June 1957 (Box 9, Folder 61A)
  - Tatsuhiko Nakano, Dept. of Chemistry, Wayne State University, June 1957-Nov. 1959 (Box 9, Folder 61B)
  - Giles Archer, Dept. of Chemistry, Wayne State University (later Stanford), "A. pyricollum alkaloid cylindrolarpine," Nov. 1958- (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Neville Finch, Chem. Dept., Wayne University, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 63A)
  - F. W. Donven, 1954-55 (Box 9, Folder 63B)
  - Neville Finch (from p. 100 ?), Stanford, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 63B)
  - Carl Swanholm (from p. 159), 1960-61 (Box 9, Folder 63B)
  - Bernaud M. Tursch, Oct. 1960- (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Ray Liedtke (from p. 153 on), May 1970- (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - David A. Lightner, Fall 1960-Fall 1962 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - David A. Lightner, Fall 1962-Fall 1964 [from index, also includes entries by W. H. Hui, 1964, and Roger Kornberg, 1964] (Box 9, Folder 65A)
  - Joseph Burakeuich, Oct. 1960-June 1963 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Sjoberg, Aug. 1958- (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Jerome E. Turse, Dept. of Chem., Stanford, Nov. 1960-Sept. 1964 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Reopened p. 266 June 21, 1972, closed Aug. 21, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - A. A. Akhrem (p. 1 only) (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Michael Seidie, Apr.-Aug., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - John Westley (p. 37 on), 1961- (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Makoto Suzuki (p. 132 on), 1962- (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - C. S. Barnes, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Michel Kaisin (p. 103 on), Jan. 1972- (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Jeanne H. Osiecki, Wayne State University, June 1957-Sept. 1960 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Harvard E. Smith, "The Elucidation of the Structure of Mycostalin," Oct. 1956-Feb. 1958 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Several unidentified people, 1961-63 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Ronald Schneider (pp. 1-119 and 295-300) (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - J. C. Knight (pp. 123-125) (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - F. K. Klein (pp. 127-176), "Alkaloid Research," Oct. 1963-June 1964 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Marcus D. Tolela (pp. 177-207), Sept. 1976-Apr. 1977 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Harvey Franklin Lodich, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - From page 95: "continued from p. 291 Book #144," Nov. 1974-Sept. 1976 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - James W. Chamberlin, July 1961-July 1963 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Dr. Haem (?), July 1961-Aug. 1962 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Joule (from p. 109 on), Sept. 1962-July 1963 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Joaquim Martins Ferreira, Aug. 1961- [entries not in English] (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Sundararaman P. (from p. 69 on), Sept. 1976- (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Phillip A. Hart, Oct. 1961-May 1963 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - W.C.M.C. Kokke (from p. 203 on), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Dr. H. Vorbruggen, Dept. of Chem., Stanford, Apr. 1961-Mar. 1963 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Autonaccio, ca. 1961-62 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Libero (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Fred J. Brown (from p. 72 on), 1976- (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Wilkinson, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Dudley H. Williams, Dept. of Chem. Stanford, Nov. 1961-Oct. 1962 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Dudley H. Williams, Dept. of Chem. Stanford, ca. Sept. 1962-Dec. 1963 (Box 11, Folder 85A)
  - Norbert Theobald (from p. 109 on), ca. 1976 (Box 11, Folder 85A)
  - L. Toues, Dec. 1961-Nov. 1967 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Catherine Clarke Fenselau, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 87A)
  - Catherine Clarke Fenselau (Box 11, Folder 87B)
  - Corella Wilimerriana (from p. 40 on), Nov. 1976- (Box 11, Folder 87B)
  - Li Hui-Ting (from p. 206 on), July 1980-May 1981 (Box 11, Folder 87B)
  - C. R. Smith, Jr., Organic Research, Wayne University, Sept. 1952-June 1955 (includes letter to Dr. Djerassi) (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - McCrindle, Burrows (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Blossey (from p. 81 on), Oct. 1962-Aug. 1963 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - V. Mutzenbecher, Stanford, Oct. 1962- (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Fajkor (from p. 156), Sept. 1963-Jan. 1964 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Unidentified (from p. 192), Nov. 1975-July 1976 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Dr. Harold Powell, Sept. 1962-Sept. 1963 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Clair Cheer (from p. 77), July 1975-May 1976 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Basil A. Burke, Jan. 1979- (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Jan E. Zielinski (from p. 209), Nov. 1979- (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Ennio Bianchi, Sept. 1962-Nov. 1963 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - E. Bianchi, July 1963- (Box 11, Folder 92A)
  - Unidentified (from p. 125), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 92A)
  - Martin Karpf (from p. 193), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 92A)
  - Robert H. Shapiro, Stanford, Oct. 1961- (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Zvi Pelah, Sept. 1960-Jan. 1964 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Donald G. Patterson, Jr. (from p. 113), Oct. 1974-July 1977 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Peter Laur, Feb.-June 1963 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Gary D. Anderson (from p. 30) (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - David J. Vanderah (from p. 150) (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Yuen-Lung Lawrence Sing (from p. 159), July-Nov 1978 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Jerry Karliner, Jan. 1963-Aug. 1964 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Keith S. Brown Jr., 1963 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Ed Warawa, Stanford, Oct. 1959- (Box 12, Folder 98A)
  - John Knight (Box 12, Folder 98B)
  - Unidentified (from p. 23), Apr. 1963- (Box 12, Folder 98B)
  - D. J. Vanderah (from p. 80), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 98B)
  - Joe Burakivich, June 1963-Apr. 1964 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Helmut Fritz (from p. 171), Feb.-Apr. 1965 [not in English] (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Bill Dow, Stanford, Oct. 1975-Apr. 1976 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - H. Wolf, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Hugo Monteira (from p. 65) (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - N. Theobald (from p. 120) (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - M. Rohmer (from p. 176), Aug. 1978-Aug. 1979 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - M. Ohashi (?), Sept. 1964-Sept. 1964 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Fred J. Brown (from p. 167), Mar. 1975-Nov. 1976 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Yuzo Nakagawa, May 1961-Oct. 1963 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Peter E. Mann, Stanford, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Paul L. Bachman, Stanford, Oct. 1965-July 1966 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Armin Walser, Dec. 1963- (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Eric Steiner (from p. 65), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Joe Konopelski (from p. 151), June 1976-Apr. 1977 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Shelia D. Sample, Feb. 1964-May 1966 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - J. P. Konopelski (from p. 160), Apr. 1974-June 1976 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Albert R. Van Horn, Stanford, Jan. 1964-June 1965 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Al Duffield, Oct. 1963-Jan. 1969 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Robin Thain Aplin (?), no dates (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Unidentified (from p. 217), Nov. 1975-Aug. 1977 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - W. Scott Briggs, Stanford, Feb. 1964-Oct. 1967 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Vandewalle, Sept. 1964-Feb. 1965 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Stephen J. Isser (from p. 71), Apr. 1966-Oct. 1967 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Kossanyi [entries in French], Sept. 1964-Mar. 1965 (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Unidentified (from p. 89), 1965- (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Unidentified (from p. 111), n.d. (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Simeon Popov (from p. 121), Sept. 1970-Jan. 1971 (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Steen Hammeuir (from p. 155), Mar. 1972- (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Reinhard R. Arndt, Sept. 1964-Aug. 1965 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Robert T. LaLonde, Sept. 1965-May 1966 (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Geraint Jones (from p. 99), Sept. 1966-Aug. 1967 (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Patridge (from p. 230), Sept.-Dec. 1976 (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - William Reusch, Sept. 1965-July 1966 (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - Michael Marx (from p. 84), Aug. 1966-Aug. 1967 (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - J. Levy, Feb. 1965- (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - S. G. Wyllie (from p. 29), Sept. 1965-July 1967 (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - Robert Walkup (from p. 181), Feb.-July 1975 (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - M. Fischer, Sept. 1964-Sept. 1965 (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - I. Rothberg (from p. 200), Sept. 1971- (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - J.K. McLeod, Sept. 1965- (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Unidentified (from p. 75), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Roger L. N. Harris, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - S. Eadon (from p. 140), Nov. 1967-Oct. 1969 (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - Wernberg, Dec. 1964-Dec. 1965 (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - A. Failli, Jan. 1965-Jan. 1966 (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - William H. Faul (from p. 92), Feb. 1966-Sept. 1967 (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Ronkins (Ronkirs?), nd. (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Grant Gill Smith (from p. 120), Sept. 1969-Aug. 1970 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Nicholas C. Ling, Stanford, Nov. 1964-June 1968 (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Frank Komitsky, Jr., Sept. 1964-Mar. 1965 (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - Ray Liedtke (from p. 111), Feb. 1968-July 1970 (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - J. B. Thomson, Oct. 1965-Aug. 1966 (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Jerry Karliner, Aug.-Dec. 1965 (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - John Diekman (from p. 35), Feb. 1966-Dec. 1967 (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Paul L. Bachman, Dec. 1965-Aug. 1966 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - J. Gore (from p. 61), ca. 1967 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - M. M. Green, Feb. 1966- (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - R. Spangler (from p. 171), Oct. 1967-June 1968 (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Peter Paul Roller, Mar. 1966-Feb. 1969 (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - James R. Trudell, July 1966-June 1968 (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - Carpenter, Sept. 1966-June 1967 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - Robertson (from p. 130), Aug. 1967-June 1968 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - W. Voelter, ca. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 134A)
  - W. Voelter, ca. 1968 (Box 15, Folder 134B)
  - Albert R. Van Horn, Stanford, June 1965-Sept. 1966 (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - I. Midgley (from p. 225), Dec. 1972-Feb. 1973 (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - Unidentified (from p. 245?), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - J. S. Muraski, Apr. 1967-Mar. 1968 (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - R. J. Suyat (from p. 69), Apr. 1969-Aug. 1971 (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - M. Karen Strong, Mar. 1967-Aug. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - Joe Keegan? (from p. 151), n.d. (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - Bill Dow? (from p. 210), July 1978-July 1979 (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - P. Brown, Oct. 1964- (Box 15, Folder 139)
  - Jill A. Moormeier (from p. 171), Oct.-Dec. 1978 (Box 15, Folder 139)
  - Ling, Aug. 1967-Mar. 1970 (Box 15, Folder 140)
  - Charles A. Brown, Sept. 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 141)
  - K. Tomer (from p. 207), Nov. 1971-Feb. 1972 (Box 15, Folder 141)
  - William H. Faul, Aug. 1967-Apr. 1969 ["go to book 155"] (Box 15, Folder 142)
  - Jacqueline Leclercq, Apr. 1967- (Box 15, Folder 143)
  - Ron Hale (from p. 121), Nov. 1968-Sept. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 143)
  - B. V. Milborrow, Chem. Dept., Stanford, Oct. 1967-Aug. 1968 (Box 15, Folder 144)
  - R. Partridge (from p. 75), Aug. 1973-Dec. 1974 (Box 15, Folder 144)
  - Adelstein, Oct. 1967-Sept. 1968 (Box 15, Folder 145)
  - John Cable (from p. 103), Oct. 1968-July 1970 (Box 15, Folder 145)
- ORD Spectra and Rotary Dispersion Notebooks, Series 3
  - Table of contents, 1-399 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ORD Spectra, 1-39 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ORD Spectra, 40-90 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ORD Spectra, 91-150 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ORD Spectra, 151-205 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ORD Spectra, 206-260 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ORD Spectra, 262-320 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Table of contents, 327-579 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ORD Spectra, 321-375 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ORD Spectra, 376-440 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ORD Spectra, 441-500 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ORD Spectra, 501-580 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - ORD data sheets, 581-604 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Table of contents, 580-749 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - ORD Spectra, 581-640 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ORD Spectra, 641-700 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - ORD Spectra, 701-749 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Table of contents, 750-870 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ORD Spectra, 750-800 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ORD Spectra, 801-850 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ORD Spectra, 851-870 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Table of contents, 871-1000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ORD Spectra, 871-920 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - ORD Spectra, 921-1000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Table of contents, 1001-1144 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ORD Spectra, 1001-1030 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ORD Spectra, 1031-1080 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ORD Spectra, 1081-1144 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Notes (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Table of contents, 1145-1322 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - ORD Spectra, 1145-1210 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ORD Spectra, 1211-1275 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ORD Spectra, 1276-1322 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Table of contents, 1401-1550 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - ORD Spectra, 1323-1449 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ORD Spectra, 1451-1520 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - ORD Spectra, 1521-1550 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Table of contents, 1551-1750 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - ORD Spectra, 1551-1610 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - ORD Spectra, 1611-1670 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - ORD Spectra, 1671-1750 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Table of contents, 1744-1954 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - ORD Spectra, 1751-1830 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - ORD Spectra, 1831-1890 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - ORD Spectra, 1891-1949 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Table of contents, 1956-2130 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - ORD Spectra, 1950-2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - ORD Spectra, 2001-2060 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - ORD Spectra, 2061-2110 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - ORD Spectra, 2111-2148 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Table of contents, 2149-2347 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - ORD Spectra, 2149-2200 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - ORD Spectra, 2201-2260 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - ORD Spectra, 2261-2299 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - ORD Spectra, 2300-2347A (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Table of contents, 2348-2599 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - ORD Spectra, 2348-2380 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ORD Spectra, 2381-2450 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ORD Spectra, 2451-2510 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ORD Spectra, 2511-2550 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - ORD Spectra, 2551-2599 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Table of Contents 2600-2774 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - ORD Spectra 2600-2640 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - ORD Spectra 2641-2700 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - ORD Spectra 2701-2774 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Table of Contents 2775-2972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - ORD Spectra 2775-2830 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - ORD Spectra 2831-2870 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - ORD Spectra 2831-2920 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - ORD Spectra 2921-2950 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - ORD Spectra 2951-2972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Table of Contents 2973-3305 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - ORD Spectra 2973-3040 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - ORD Spectra 3041-3080 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - ORD Spectra 3081-3130 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - ORD Spectra 3131-3190 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - ORD Spectra 3191-3240 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - ORD Spectra 3241-3305 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Table of Contents 3306-3499, 3600-3809 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - ORD Spectra 3306-3360 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - ORD Spectra 3361-3420 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - ORD Spectra 3421-3480 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - ORD Spectra 3481-3490 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - ORD Spectra 3642-3680 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - ORD Spectra 3681-3740 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ORD Spectra 3741-3808 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Table of Contents 3500-3559 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - ORD Spectra 3531-3559 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - ORD Spectra 3500-3530 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Table of Contents 3810-4055 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - ORD Spectra 3809-3890 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - ORD Spectra 3891-3970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - ORD Spectra 3972-4050 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - ORD Spectra 4051-4130 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - ORD Spectra 4134-4199 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - ORD Spectra 4200-4257 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - ORD Spectra 4262-4330 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - ORD Spectra 4331-4422B (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Rotary Dispersions - Table of Contents J01-J0184 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Rotary Dispersions J01-J070 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Rotary Dispersions J071-J0120 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Rotary Dispersions J0121-J0184 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Removed (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Removed (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Removed (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - William D. Closson - Triterpenes (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - William Closson - Spectropolarimetric Curves - Triterpenes + Related Compounds (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - William Closson - SpectropolarimetricRecords #! (Ketones) (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Research Grant Files, Series 4
  - 105 NIH Postdoctoral Supply, 1969-1976 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
  - 485 Mass Spec, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
  - 487 Marine Chemistry, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - 490 Novel Sterols, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 8-10)
  - 492 Mass Spec, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
  - 494 Marine Chemistry, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 13-14)
  - 495 MCD, 1981-1984 (Box 19, Folder 15-17)
  - 498 CD of Cyclic Ketones, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 18-20)
  - 500 Mass Spec, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 21-23)
  - 501 Dendral, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 24-26)
  - 504 Marine Chemistry, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 27-29)
  - 506 MCD, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 30-32)
  - 507 Biomedical M/S Fund, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 33-34)
  - 602 Chemistry Research Fund, 1975-1983 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  - 603 Syntex, 1977-1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 708-712 University of Minnesota, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 5-13)
  - 509 Mass Spec, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 14-16)
  - 511 Marine Chemistry, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 17-19)
  - 512 MCD NIH, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 20-22)
  - 516 Mass Spec, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 23-25)
  - 517 Marine Chemistry, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 26-30)
  - Chemical Investigation of Brazilian Insects and Plants, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Magnetic and Optical Circular Dichroism Studies of Organic Molecules, 1967-1969 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Low Temperature CD Studies, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Chemical Investigation of Brazilian Insects and Plants, 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Mass Spectrometry in Organic Biochemistry, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Application for Renewal, 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Research on Alkaloids GM 11309-06, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Research on Alkaloids GM 11309-01, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Research on Alkaloids GM 11309-02, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Research on Alkaloids GM 11309-03, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Research on Alkaloids GM 11309-04, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Research on Alkaloids GM 11309-05, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - MCD proposal to Dr. Miller--Stanford University, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Research on Terpenoids GM 06840-05, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Research on Terpenoids GM 06840-06, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Research on Terpenoids GM 06840-07, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Research on Terpenoids GM 06840-08, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Research on Terpenoids GM 06840-09, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Research on Terpenoids GM 06840-10, 1968-1973 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Research on Terpenoids GM 06840-10, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Research on Terpenoids GM 06840-11, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Research on Terpenoids GM 06840-12, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Research on Terpenoids GM 06840-13, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Steroid Studies AM 12758-09, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Steroid Studies AM 12758-08, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Steroid Studies AM 12758-07, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Steroid Studies AM 12758-06, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Studies on Steroids and Related Compounds, 1968-1973 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Steroid Studies CA 07195-05, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Steroid Studies in Cancer CA 07195-04, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Steroid Studies in Cancer CA 07195-03, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Steroid Studies in Cancer CA 07195-02, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Steroid Studies in Cancer CA 07195-01, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - New Instrumentation Methods in Structural Elucidation GM 12173-06, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - New Insturmentation Methods in Structural Elucidation GM 12173-05, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - New Instrumentation Methods in Structural Elucidation GM 12173-04, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - New Instrumentation in Structural Elucidation GM 12173-03, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - New Insturmentation in Strcutural Elucidation GM 12173-02, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - New Instrumentation in Structural Elucidation GM 12173-03, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - NIH AM12758 2 FBE-405, 1963-1974 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 5 R01 AM17896-02, 1974-1977 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - NATO #939 2 FBE-607, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Syntex Corporation, 1972-1975 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Grant, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - NIH -75-C-59 NIH Heart and Lung Institute, Mass Spectra, 1974-1977 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Research fellowships, active proposals, 1968-1976 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - American Chemical Society, denied proposal, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - 523 Mass Spec, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 9-10)
  - 524 Marine, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 11-12)
  - 525 MCD, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 13-14)
  - 527 Marine, 1987-1989 (Box 42, Folder 15-16)
  - 528 Mass Spec, 1987-1988 (Box 42, Folder 17-18)
  - 608 Chemistry Research Fund, 1981-1986 (Box 42, Folder 19-21)
  - 609 Chevron, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Expense allocation, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Expense allocation, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Expense allocation, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Symposia, Series 5
  - Fall 1972 symposium: "Effects of Regulatory Agencies on Scientific and Industrial Productivity" (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - "Student's View of Industry,", 1971 Apr 23-24 (Box 1, Folder 6-9)
  - Spring Symposium: "Does Chemistry Have a Future in Chemistry Departments?" (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Spring Symposium, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
  - Industrial Affiliates Program: Miscellaneous, to July 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14-19)
  - Industrial Affiliates Program: Miscellaneous, to July 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Industrial Affiliates Program: Potential Members (Box 2, Folder 3-10)
  - Stanford Chemistry Department: General Memoranda (Box 2, Folder 11-15)
- Mass Spectra Notebooks, Series 6 (Box 28-41)
  - Adelstein (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anderson (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Antonaccio (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Aplin (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Archer (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arndt (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bachman (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Barnes (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bianchi (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Blossey (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Brewer (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Briggs (1) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Briggs (2) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Brown, C. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Brown, F. (1) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Brown, F. (2) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Brown, F. (3) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Brown, K. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Brown, P. (1) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Brown, P. (2) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Brown, P. (3) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Brown, P. (4) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Brown, S. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Burakervich (1) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Burakevich (2) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Burke (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Burrows (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cable (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Carpenter (1) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Carpenter (2) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chamberlain (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Cook, M. (1) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Cook, M. (2) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Crossley (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Diekman (1) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Diekman (2) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Diekman (3) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Eadon (1) (Box 3, Folder 8)